const STORE = {
    questions: [
        {
            question: "Mollusca is the __ largest phylum of invertebrate animals?",
            options: [
                "second",
                "third",
                "tenth",
                "hundredth"
            ],
            answer: "second"
        },
        {
            question: "There are about __ recognized species of mollusk.",
            options: [
                "500",
                "15,000",
                "85,000",
                "1.25 million"
            ],
            answer: "85,000"
        },
        {
            question: "Mollusks are the largest marine phylum, comprising about __ of all the named marine organisms.",
            options: [
                "52%",
                "38%",
                "10%",
                "23%"
            ],
            answer: "23%"
        },
        {
            question: "The word mollusk originated from the Latin <i>molluscus</i>, from mollis, meaning what?",
            options: [
                "Slippery",
                "Soft",
                "Short",
                "Smooth"
            ],
            answer: "Soft"
        },
        {
            question: "Of the 9 commonly recognized classes of mollusks, how many are extinct?",
            options: [
                "2",
                "5",
                "7",
                "none"
            ],
            answer: "2"
        },
        {
            question: "The __ account for about 80% of the total classified species.",
            options: [
                "Gastropods",
                "Bivalves",
                "Cephalopods",
                "Monoplacophorans"
            ],
            answer: "Gastropods"
        },
        {
            question: "Which class of mollusk are among the most neurologically advanced of all invertebrates?",
            options: [
                "Gastropods",
                "Cephalopods",
                "Scaphopods",
                "Polyplacophores"
            ],
            answer: "Cephalopods"
        },
        {
            question: "The __ is the largest known invertebrate species.",
            options: [
                "Giant African Snail",
                "Giant Clam",
                "Giant Shipworm",
                "Colossal Squid"
            ],
            answer: "Colossal Squid"
        },
        {
            question: "Good evidence suggests that mollusks first appeared in what time period?",
            options: [
                "Cambrian",
                "Triassic",
                "Devonian",
                "Neogene"
            ],
            answer: "Cambrian"
        },
        {
            question: "Which of these anatomical features is unique to mollusks?",
            options: [
                "Antenna",
                "Radula",
                "Gill",
                "Spinneret"
            ],
            answer: "Radula"
        },
    ],
    currentQuestion: 0,
    score: 0
};